

Phone: 09559610243

Email: raianjali280397@gmail.com

Website: https://condescending-heisenberg-a12f9b.netlify.app/

Address: D 57/49 C-2 Plot No. 9, Maulvi Bagh Sonia Road, Sigra Varanasi

PROFILE

Motivated software engineering graduate from the Institute of Engineering and Technology, Lucknow with almost 3 years' experience in software industry. AWS Cloud Practitioner Certified. Seeking to use proven sl Python and project management to meet business needs.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
- Appeared and qualified in NITAT exam conducted by IIT BOMBAY in C, C++ and lava.
- Participated in Core Java workshop and bagged 1st prize.

SKILLS

Java | Python

JavaScript | PHP

C | C++

SQL | Data Structure | Problem-Solving

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap

Django | Laravel | Spring

ReactJS

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Application [Jul 2018 - Sept 2020] Institute of Engineering and Technology, Lucknow | 8.9 CGPA Aug

Bachelor of Computer Application [2015 - Jun 2018] School of Management Sciences, Varanasi | 74.69%

Intermediate [Apr 2013 - May 2014] Central Hindu Girls School, Varanasi | 76% High School [Jul 2011 - Jun 2012] Central Hindu Girls School, Varanasi | 9.8 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBM [SYSTEM ENGINEER]

[Jan 2021 - Present]

- Worked in the areas of SailPoint IdentityIQ, J2EE, Java, XML, JSP, Servlets, spring, MySQL.
- Developed rules to integrate the various connectors in SailPoint to pull the data from various resources.
- Worked on Web Services, REST and XML technologies.
- Developed custom Java classes in SailPoint IIQ.
- Create, develop, and track solutions to application errors reported.
- Note interruptions or bugs in operation and carry out mitigation / problem management.

EZOPS INC. [SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN]

[Sep 2020 - Jan 2021]

- Involved in the design and development phases of Agile Software Development.
- Developed java modules implementing business rules and workflows using Spring Boot.
- Worked extensively with the backend which comprised of Spring, Hibernate and IPA
- Worked on code in python (pandas) to manipulate data in excel sheet in order to perform reconciliation.

XELPMOC DESIGN AND TECHNOLOGY LTD. [SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN]

[Mar 2020 - Sep 2020]

- Designed And developed a Restful APIs for different modules in the project as per the requirement.
- Developed web pages using HTML, CSS, React, JSON, Bootstrap.
- All the functionality is implemented using Spring Boot and Hibernate ORM.
 Implemented Java EE components using Spring MVC, Spring IOC, Spring Transaction and Spring Security Module.

PROJECTS

ACADEZY

Have worked as a back-end developer. Designed and maintained the database. Created REST APIs. Tested the full working of the application.

ARC

Performed reconciliation using the product ARO for multiple clients and have created plugins using python and java modules using Spring

SailPoint

Worked on well-organized, optimized, and documented source code. Debug existing source code. Continuously learn and improve skills. Attentive to details, and carried out tasks with high standards.